{
    "subject": "Guy_Ritchie",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Hire",
    "human_readable": "Guy Ritchie directed The Hire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.85654217004776,
            "question": "What is Guy Ritchie known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459610104560852,
            "question": "What are some other films directed by Guy Ritchie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103869318962097,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Hire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3149593770503998,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Hire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2514944076538086,
            "question": "When was 'The Hire' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20664365589618683,
            "question": "Is 'The Hire' a movie or a television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18580438196659088,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'The Hire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1337493658065796,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'The Hire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11411628872156143,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Hire' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10614080727100372,
            "question": "Has 'The Hire' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Guy Ritchie directed The Hire.",
            "html": "yago_28271_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'The Hire' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_28271_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch 'The Hire'?",
            "html": "yago_28271_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in 'The Hire'?",
            "html": "yago_28271_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28271_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided suggest that Guy Ritchie has directed several films and commercials, but one of his works mentioned in the context information is indeed a short movie called \"Star\" which was part of the series \"The Hire\". Therefore, the triple \"Guy Ritchie directed The Hire\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Guy Ritchie directed The Hire.\" Specifically, one of the documents mentions that Guy Ritchie is known for his crime films and directs various projects including \"The Hire,\" which is described as a series of short movies where he directs stories involving Clive Owen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}